Hello Hello friends welcome to us
because the channel Indian Raju Punjabi is a
C machine among our teams, it is very important for them
or right now in today's date, an
important service has
just been closed due to which there are CSP operators of many
things related to us that are going to be launched, with regard to this,
I am going to
tell you the whole thing in this video, let's
start this video,
before starting I would request you if
you have not yet subscribed to my YouTube channel,
please subscribe,
so let's first
see the important announcement,
what is written in it
[music],
but friends, on the login page of the people,
here in the ticket update, you will get a new update to
see, last means so that you
can see, so I will open it further, it is in
front of you, it is important, if an ad is written in it, then
I will tell you about it,
but it is written in it that ICICI
Bank and two wheeler and four wheeler policy will be
effective today itself 4th
June 21, meaning what essence which
Lambert has through our sewing  The two wheeler or four
wheeler insurance policy that was done has been
discontinued from today itself, it will
not be available on your portal right now, I
searched for it after some time and found it here, there is
no guarantee as to when it will come in future, whether it will
come or not in future, it is
okay to ask about it, if it was written in the
serial number two wheeler four wheeler
insurance product will be visible from
today's date 4th June 2012, it is
written in the requested to send that from the 24th of this,
whatever this loan is, both of them have been discontinued,
due to some regular checking, new
nominations start coming in this
product, idol worshippers, half
in this scheme, which means if
any new pharmacy of this four wheeler does not register you,
that means you will not be able to do any new inchase of anyone,
due to this the will communicate
straight away, secretary and CT enable unknown,
later Pappu will be informed separately
whenever the label is there, it has been started here, now you
people can do Star Insurance policy,
yes this is mortgage claim settlement of the  The
existing policy will not have any effect and
the process is criminal only, you people have
insured your two wheeler and four wheeler before this, no
one will do anything about it, the
way it is going will be fine for me, that will be fine,
but you will not do a new policy right now
and there is no date confirmed in this yet,
it is only on the front, that it has been
doubled permanently, sometimes it will go live, there will be
lighting, this line, but its
gate is not clear right now, that it is very important for
Saudi saints because we do
insurance policy for many machines and two wheelers,
for them there is no such side
because their mode will get stuck down, so if
you people liked today's imported latest news video, then
definitely
like and share this video and definitely subscribe to my channel
because I
always keep bringing new videos on such other sides, there is a
plate going to be